<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Code feels</title>
        <link>https://codefeels.github.io</link>
        <description>Blog by Code Feels</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 23:55:21 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>n/a</copyright>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A sad parallel in work relationships and personal relationships]]></title>
            <link>https://codefeels.github.io/posts/2022-11-13-parallels</link>
            <guid>https://codefeels.github.io/posts/2022-11-13-parallels</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 id="in-my-job-i-often-butt-heads-with-my-boss"><a aria-hidden="true" tabindex="-1" href="#in-my-job-i-often-butt-heads-with-my-boss"><a href="#in-my-job-i-often-butt-heads-with-my-boss" style="margin-right: 10px">#</a></a>In my job, I often butt heads with my boss.</h2>
<p>I feel like my boss rarely has a clue for what is right for our project. I feel
he is very aloof. And I feel like his engagement with important situations is
often fairly shallow. I feel very stressed out and frayed very constantly,
while I think my boss feels very little of this, and he often gives overly
optimistic outlooks.</p>
<h2 id="with-my-partner-at-home-there-is-a-disturbing-parallel"><a aria-hidden="true" tabindex="-1" href="#with-my-partner-at-home-there-is-a-disturbing-parallel"><a href="#with-my-partner-at-home-there-is-a-disturbing-parallel" style="margin-right: 10px">#</a></a>With my partner at home, there is a disturbing parallel</h2>
<p>I often have not very much engagement on domestic issues such as for example,
travel, lodging, etc. I just think everything is fine, and whatever ends up
happening is ok. And yet, my girlfriend is often running very high stress about
these issues. She claims that I don't listen to her, and is often extremely
annoyed by the input that I do have.</p>
<h2 id="whats-the-conclusion-or-resolution-to-these-issues"><a aria-hidden="true" tabindex="-1" href="#whats-the-conclusion-or-resolution-to-these-issues"><a href="#whats-the-conclusion-or-resolution-to-these-issues" style="margin-right: 10px">#</a></a>What's the conclusion or resolution to these issues?</h2>
<p>I do not know. In my job, I need to chill the fuck out or find a better
solution than butting heads all the time. Same thing in my personal life, yet
in that case, I feel like I am not the fight-seeker.</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Waiting for feedback]]></title>
            <link>https://codefeels.github.io/posts/2021-12-07-waiting</link>
            <guid>https://codefeels.github.io/posts/2021-12-07-waiting</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sometimes, basically removing the enhancement, or disabling it, will fix it</p>
<p>So, I oftentimes will make a PR to this effect and say, "here is a fix, it
basically removes the enhancement, and fixes a bug. This is a bug users
definitely will definitely run into, so we should probably merge this and
release it so that they don't run into it". what I normally get in response to
this is crickets</p>
<p>I can guess at some reasons why my coworkers are avoiding this issue maybe. For
example</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>they don't want to "duplicate work" by undoing the enhancement on the master
branch (and later redoing it)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>they have pride in their feature and don't want to see it undone</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>they are trying to be sensitive to the feelings of the person who originally
developed the enhancement, and avoid undoing it</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>they are not "satisfied" with the PR that removes the enhancement, and would
rather see a fix to the enhancement</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>The reality though is there is often very little feedback on these PRs that I
make, so I just have to sit around with anxiety. There are currently at least 3
of these on my codebase from enhancements I did not make, but which I created
fixes for that basically rollback portions of these enhancements. Oftentimes
took me pretty deep debugging to even figure out that one weird enhancement had
such a weird knock on effect to create bug X and so with the silence from my
team, i feel unappreciated in addition to all this.</p>
<p>This is, perhaps, not really unique to my particular scenario. The feelings
that I get from this, anxiety and feeling unappreciated, can happen in many
other scenarios, exacerbated by remote work, pandemic, team culture, etc. I
hope to work to make things better somehow though</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>